Well, apparently I've discovered that
I can take these yawn-filled days
And turn them into movies
I've found the secret and trick to it
Under this sky where we don't get along
I closed my heart and locked it
That's how I've managed to live my life
And the melodies now overlap
I wanted a sign, no matter how small
That I could actually find
better than any streetlight
I put a ribbon on each of the
sights that my eyes pick out
And I collect them like souvenirs
as I continue down this path home
The seasons each say hello,
and I shed a few tears as I go
Where should I begin to talk about
this way home that you've given me?
I walk and walk and sometimes
rush on my way to see you
I run and run, wait, no, I should
still walk on my way to see you
CARRY OUT THE GRIFFIN PLAN
Morning, Anya!
Morning, pwease, Becky.
Did you see yesterday's
episode of Berlint in Love?
The two characters finally reunited
after overcoming so many obstacles!
Oh, and my heart just wouldn't stop pounding
at the embrace scene with Vincent!
I like cartoons more than dramas.
Oh, you're still such a child, Anya.
You're probably not interested
in romance at all, are you?
I take back what I said about you being mature.
Are you talking about flirty stuff?
I guess you're too young to understand yet.
If you have love, you can even fly!
Liar.
You never know when it'll happen.
Hmph! Look at them getting all excited over
something so stupid first thing in the morning.
Our midterms are coming up soon, too.
I wonder if those two are even studying.
Oh, Second Son.
Previously on SPY x FAMILY...
Second Son couldn't understand
how awesome Bond is,
meaning Anya had failed
the Friendship Scheme.
If you can think up an
awesome name for your dog,
He never said this
I'll let you come over to my house.
Second Son's House
Will Anya be able to overcome
Second Son's bullying
and complete her mission?
Anya's battle continues.
Fank you very much for watching.
So for that reason,
I brought a secret weapon today.
I asked Papa yesterday to have another
family photo taken, this time with Bond.
If I show him this...
Whoa! What the heck is this giant dog?
Let's battle to see whose dog is stronger!
I'm sorry for ignoring you the other day.
His name is Bond.
Oh, noes.
I have dropped the photo with
my very cool dog in it.
Anya is so clumsy...
The range of possible questions
for the exam is so wide.
It really is!
Shock!
Oh, for crying out loud. Just leave them be!
This is why a mature guy is so
much better than those children.
Oh, come on, Anya. You dropped something.
He's so amazing...
Who in the world is this
unbelievably hot guy?!
Are you telling me this is your father?
Hello?! You never told me about him!
Introduce me to him!
Well? What's his name? Is he
seeing someone right now?
Papa is married to Mama!
Hey, I'll be keeping this picture, okay?
Thank you!
Give that back! I need to show Second Son!
He's so hot!
Ugh! They're so obnoxious.
We will now begin your
arts and crafts class,
but because Master Rodin is out sick today,
I will be acting as your
substitute instructor.
Your assignment today will be making
a 3D object out of these materials.
The theme will be "animals."
First, we will be randomly
dividing you into groups.
Each group will only be given
a limited number of resources,
so you will need to discuss their
use with your groupmates.
Yes, sir.
Group one: Herman Clark,
Edward Perkshire, Paler Nomney...
This sounds like a fun class!
What are you going to make?
I'm—
Hmph. This is some dumb kid's game.
I don't have time for this.
A-Absolutely!
I heard from someone in Class 2 that
important people from the school are
going to come look at our projects.
Wow... This might actually
affect our grades.
Hmm... I guess I'll take
this somewhat seriously.
Hey, you two. Don't hold me back
if we end up in the same group.
Uh...
Next, group four:
Damian Desmond, Anya Forger...
This is my chance!
God damn it!
I had a feeling this would happen!
You! Don't you dare think
of getting in my way!
Aw, we ended up in different groups, Anya.
Gimme back the picture.
I need to show Second Son.
What?
But you said I could have it.
I did not!
Make sure you give me a different
photo if you have one!
I say, have a seat, you two.
Now I'll just have to...
use these materials...
to create a cool-looking Bond
and show it off to Second Son.
All right, begin.
I'm going to make a bunny!
Me, too!
Do you have enough paper?
Let me see that pen next.
Of course, their creativity
and ability to share
limited materials within a group
will affect their marks,
but we must truly pay attention
to their restraint.
Cooperation, flexibility, enthusiasm,
and uniqueness are also...
Hmm?
Becky Blackbell, what is that you're making?
It's Anya's father!
Loid Forger?! This is too unique!
Also, you can put on the combat suit
my family's company is making...
As an optional item!
Er, I commend you for
your elegant creativity,
but I told you the theme was "animals."
Start over!
Master Henderson...
In the end, humans are animals, too.
'Tis true!
Very well. I'll allow this, Blackbell.
You win this time.
Oh, but my sweet Loid must be
a super-intellectual person,
so calling him an animal is rude.
I'll make something else.
Huh?!
Finished!
His name is Bond.
So you're into naming garbage?
Operation Dog has reached its end.
What operation? Also, that
was supposed to be a dog?
What are you making, Lord Damian?
Hm?
A griffin, just like the one in my family crest.
Impressive as ever, Lord Damian!
What an outstanding choice!
Griffin?
Are they related to Mister Chimera?
I'm going to need a lot of paper,
so you guys better use it sparingly.
Huh?
But of course!
Since my family name is involved,
I can't make anything bad.
I know! If I can make this thing amazing...
Father, look.
I created the heraldic beast
of the Desmond family.
Oho, quite impressive indeed.
You've accurately depicted our
family's dignity and elegance.
You are truly the pride of
the Desmond family, Damian.
If only...
Second Son, Anya will help
you make your griffin!
Really? You're so nice!
Thank you!
Look, Father! Isn't this griffin amazing?
Miss Anya helped make half of it!
You have excellent taste, Anya!
I would love to see your
parents! Bring them here!
Mission complete.
Operation Dog is now
Operation Griffin. It's perfect.
Huh?
Will I have enough time and
materials to finish it, though?
These wings are gonna be a pain.
Second Son.
Huh?
Anya will help you make that thing.
You can use my paper.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Make your own!
I'm already done.
You're going to turn that in? Are you insane?!
I want to help you out.
F-F-F...
Fine! Whatever!
Ooh, what's this? Is that
what's going on, Anya?
I was wondering why she was
so obsessed with him.
Then you can make its hind legs.
Okey-dokey.
Oh? So they're going to make
a masterpiece together.
Most intriguing, Forger and Desmond.
All done.
Huh? What are those?
I told you to make legs.
I made it jet engines so it can go zoom!
No one asked you to put weird stuff on it!
Never mind! Make the feathers instead!
Leave it to me.
Ta-da!
Don't "ta-da" me!
They're all sloppy and uneven!
Do you really think it can fly
with that many feathers?!
Don't worry. It has jet engines,
so it can still fly.
I'm not using those!
Just butt out! How could you
waste this much paper?!
You're so useless!
Shock!
Damian, I think that's a little harsh.
Shut up! Hand over your paper, too!
What?
I cannot let this pass!
Not elegant!
Would you call your actions
gentlemanly, Desmond?
But... Damn it.
It's no use. I won't be able to complete
it properly because of that shrimp.
I really wanted to show this to Father.
You do not need to rush, Desmond.
Just do everything you can
within your limits right now.
But that's not enough!
Time is up!
Make sure you line up your
creations in the hallway.
Hey, look!
Your giraffe's legs are so stubby.
Well, look at that ridiculous
mane on your lion!
My creation is clearly the best!
Second Son... I'm sorry I was so useless.
You can have this instead of the feathers.
Huh?
What is this? It's just the garbage you made.
I turned it into a girl griffin!
Make it a pair with yours!
Huh? Why do I need to add that to it?
A...
Apparently, if you have love, you can fly.
Huh?
Oho. Are these the sculptures
from our first graders?
They are all quite adorable.
Th-This is...
Huh?
That sculpture... won the top prize?
One of the officials from the board of
education was quite impressed with it.
"The fact that it still looked so regal
despite having its wings torn apart
made me think that our country still had a
future and could recover from this war."
Huh? Uh, right...
That piece of garbage? Really?
Impressive as ever, Lord Damian!
Good form!
Apparently, he couldn't hold back his tears
when he saw the corpse of the
innocent baby griffin next to it.
Th-That's great. You can
show it off to your father.
All according to plan!
Huh?
Like I could ever show that
pathetic thing to my father!
Shock!
Operation Griffin... has ended.
Hello?
Yes, Jeeves, it's me.
That elephant was really weird, wasn't it?
Yes. I'm fine. Is Max well?
It was so long.
Yes. Will you be returning during break?
No... Father won't be home anyway, will he?
He... will not.
But Master Demmy will be returning home.
I have exams coming up, so I'll stay
here to concentrate on my studies.
Brilliant, Young Master Dammy.
Oh, right. Today, in arts and crafts class...
Hm?
No, never mind.
Jeeves... You told Father about
my orientation, didn't you?
Did he say anything about it?
Why, yes, he did.
He was quite worried about your health.
You liar.
I see. Thanks.
I'm going to go now.
Father has never worried about me.
I'm telling you, that was just a coincidence!
Ewen, Emile...
Oh, Lord Damian!
Are you done with your phone call?
Yeah. Once we're done eating, let's study
for our exams with some instructors.
But of course!
Let's concentrate most on English,
since it's your weakest subject.
Shut up.
I guess...
I really will have to become
an Imperial Scholar.
The top prize...
The top prize?
Sylvia Sherwood.
A handler at WISE, the Westalis
Intelligence Services Eastern-Focused division.
Age: ■■. Single.
Officially, she performs duties as an
attaché at Westalis's embassy in the East.
And unofficially, she commands
a number of intelligence agents
despite being under strict
surveillance by the Secret Police.
Because of her constantly
flawless performance,
her agents call her "Fullmetal Lady,"
and are in awe of her.
FULLMETAL LADY
We will now begin our operation to
tail Westalis's Secretary Sherwood.
I should praise them for
their persistence, at least.
The same clothes, the same shop,
the same route...
Every Wednesday, I go to the public pool.
Having continuously been
shown Sylvia's routine,
their slow little minds come to a halt.
The same ol' pool...
She's gonna be in there for at least an hour.
Guess we can get some food.
As long as I can create some free time,
being able to act freely
is not a difficult task,
despite being in the enemy nation.
Now, then. I should head to
my meeting spot with Twilight.
And then the fool tripped and fell flat.
What an idiot.
This coat I just bought isn't half bad.
Fools who let down their guard
cannot survive in this world.
Good day, or perhaps good evening,
Agent Twilight.
That covers the details of the
Desmond camp's financial reports.
One of them is a paper company,
and though their public numbers are low...
I can't tell her...
that her brand-new coat still has the tag on it.
I just...
could never tell the Fullmetal
Lady, the Handler, that.
Loid Forger. Code name: Twilight.
A WISE agent who always pulls off his
missions and wants nothing but peace.
An aloof spy who threw away any
chance at normal happiness.
Every meeting with the Handler
puts our lives at stake.
If there is anyone tailing the Handler,
we must naturally shake them off.
Two to the north, and one to the east.
Shall we cancel?
No, we will meet at Point C.
Let's take care of this quickly.
Roger.
This is how we exchange information
every day to preserve the peace
between the East and West.
Good day, or perhaps good evening,
Agent Twilight.
Report your progress with Operation Strix.
My daughter...
can now clear two levels on the jump box.
She can also now jump
rope five times in a row.
What in the world is he on about?
Omelet Rice♥
Yuri! I tried to cook something!
Here's some omelet rice!
Wow, that's amazing, Sis!
I have no idea what this
substance could be!
Down the hatch!
Please wait a little while
Yum!
It's so good, Sis! Barf!
Oh, that's wonderful!
I'll try to make you home-cooked
meals from now on!
I tried making some cream-sauce pasta.
Wow! Nothing here resembles pasta at all!
That's amazing!
Ta-da! Here's some cake!
Wow! I've never seen cake
so blue! That's amazing!
Sis, you're such an amazing cook,
I bet you can get married in no time!
Oh, stop!
Yuri!
And so this man obtained an invincible body.
So you were dizzy because you'd
stayed up for four nights
and then got run over by a truck yesterday.
Be more careful.
I'm perfectly fine.
UNCLE THE PRIVATE TUTOR
DAYBREAK